export const questionAndAnswer = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "How long can the cookies be kept for?",
    answer:
      "The cookies are best eaten within 12 hours or can be stored in the fridge for 3 days but reheated at 150C for 3-5 minutes before serving. For prolonged storage, the cookies can also be freezed for up to 2 weeks and reheated at 150C for 5-7 minutes before serving. The sable cookies are best eaten within 1 month, unopened or stored in airtight container. To be kept in cool & dry place.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Are the cookies halal?",
    answer:
      "Our cookies use only non-meat based ingredients and there is no alcohol or gelatin used. We do not have the official halal certification but most of our ingredients are in fact from hala certified suppliers.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Are the cookies vegetarian?",
    answer:
      "Our cookies use only non-meat based ingredients but we use eggs in our cookies so it depends on how strict the vegetarian diet is!",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "I'm sending the cookies to multiple friends. Can I request for specific ways to pack my order?",
    answer:
      "Yes, of course! You can Whatsapp us at 96272028 or email us at hello@folksandstories.com to let us know your requests. do note that for delivery, we will most likely pack the items into a bigger carrier, but separate the cookies based on your request. This is to optimize the delivery size of the order, ensure the cookies are packed well and that there is no extra delivery charges. We will include extra bags for you according to the number of recipients you'va indicated!",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Is there a self-collection option?",
    answer:
      "Yes, you may select the self-collection option when checking out. The collection time from Monday to Friday is 10-5pm.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "What happens if a delivery failed due to incomplete address or if the recipient is unable to receive?",
    answer:
      "There is a grace period of 15 mins once the courier arrives at the destination. If recipient/ sender is uncontactable, the courier would have to leave to continue with other deliveries. We try our best to re-deliver on the same day, however this is subject to the availbaility of our delivery schedule and re-delivery charges will apply. If there is no update on the day of delivery, the order will be cancelled and no refund will be made.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "What happens if I have issues with the order delivered (eg. missing/ damaged item)?",
    answer:
      "For issue with missing item, we require photos of full order delivered in its original conditions, along with your order number. With that, we will proceed to investigate and once confirmed, we will refund the amount accordingly. \n For issue with damaged item, we require photos of all such items. Only item(s) shown in the photos will be considered for compensation. \n Please note that feedback of such issues needs to be made within 48 hours from receipt of order. Once 48 hours has lapsed, the issue will be handled on a goodwill basis. Rest assured, we always try our best to bake and deliver our cookies in its best condition!",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Is it possible for me to make any changes to my order?",
    answer:
      "Yes, you're able to do so with at least 3 working days notice prior to the selected delivery date. However, if your order change results in a lower value than your original order, there is a non-refundable 3.8% fee chraged by the online payment gateway for the value difference.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Is it possible for me to cancel an order?",
    answer:
      "Yes, you're able to do so with at least 3 working days notice prior to the selected delivery date. However, do note that there is a non-refundable 3.8% fee charged by the online payment gateway.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What are the options for customisation?",
    answer:
      "Please contact us at enquiry@flourpower.sg to find out more about customisations.",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "What are the charges for customisations?",
    answer:
      "Please contact us at enquiry@flourpower.sg to find out more about customisations.",
  },
];
